<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Fundamentals &amp; Infrastructure on Cloud Native Security</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Fundamentals &amp; Infrastructure on Cloud Native Security</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Deployment Models: Public, Private, and Hybrid Clouds Explained</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/cloud-deployment-models-public-private-and-hybrid-clouds-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/cloud-deployment-models-public-private-and-hybrid-clouds-explained/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkCloud deployment models refer to the different ways cloud services can be deployed and accessed. These models—public, private, and hybrid—offer varying levels of control, security, and flexibility. This tutorial will explore each cloud deployment model, outlining their key characteristics and security implications.&#xA;Public Cloud linkA public cloud is a cloud computing environment owned and operated by a third-party provider, making resources available to the general public over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Service Models: IaaS, PaaS, and SaaS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/understanding-cloud-service-models-iaas-paas-and-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/understanding-cloud-service-models-iaas-paas-and-saas/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkCloud computing has revolutionized the way businesses and individuals access and manage IT resources. Understanding the different cloud service models is crucial for making informed decisions about deploying and securing applications and data in the cloud. This tutorial explores the three primary cloud service models: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS), focusing on their key features and security implications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtualization Technologies and Security: A Deep Dive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/virtualization-technologies-and-security-a-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cloud-native-security/docs/infra/infra/virtualization-technologies-and-security-a-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkVirtualization is a fundamental technology that underpins cloud computing, enabling the creation of multiple virtual environments on a single physical server. This tutorial explores the core concepts of virtualization, focusing on popular tools like VirtualBox and VMware Workstation, and delves into the security implications of using virtualization technologies.&#xA;Understanding Virtualization linkVirtualization allows you to create and run multiple virtual machines (VMs) on a single physical machine, each with its own operating system and applications.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
